You like me as a friend, right?
What do you think?
Something good happen?
You kept your bed hair intact.
Mayama, you've become best buds with Asamiya.
Smells like Asamiya.
What do you think of him?
I guess he feels far away?
If Asamiya feels so far, then get close!
You only "like" me as a friend, right?
Of course not.
We took it too far. Sorry!
Can we be friends, too?
- Huh?
- Let's join the planning committee.
Planning committee?
Brilliant idea.
You weren't put off by the idea?
I hope we didn't force you
onto the planning committee.
Asamiya's "like"
was not as a friend.
A guy like Asamiya
is way out of my league.
A haunted house!
The results are in.
Our class will be doing...
a haunted house for the culture festival!
- That was a close poll.
- For sure.
- Too bad our butler cafe idea didn't win.
- Yeah.
If anything...
Welcome home, milady.
I thought it had plenty of potential.
I guess it ultimately works out, though.
Asamiya prefers to work backstage anyway.
Yeah, our cafe would hinge
on him working up front.
I bet Mayama wanted to see
Asamiya's butler fit, too.
No, I...
Yes, I voted for the butler cafe. Sorry.
I'd dress up for Mayama.
Anyway, I'll be working backstage
for the haunted house as well.
Sure thing.
Maybe we can shop for costumes this weekend?
Yeah, we'll need fits for our various scares.
Mayama, hope you're ready
to spook our guests.
Sure, I'll do my best.
I'm hyped.
Same. What should I dress as?
How do I look?
Stylish.
Thanks for the clothes.
My little brother,
hanging out with friends...
I'm glad we picked the farther away school.
We're just grabbing supplies together.
I'm more surprised
you wanted a proper outfit.
Let me guess.
There's someone in the group
who catches your eye?
Just kidding. I know it's an all-boys school.
Yeah.
You only "like" me
as a friend, right?
Like you "like" everyone else.
Of course not.
Hare?
We're just going shopping.
I know.
- So are you good on time?
- Huh?
Crap. See you later!
Have fun!
Just made it.
Mayama.
Something wrong?
Sorry. You just look... different, today.
Do I really?
Uh, I mean...
Where's Sakaki and Tsunekawada?
They're running late.
They went to grab some props first.
I see.
Your clothes make you look older.
Is that weird?
These are my brother's,
so they're a bit baggy.
You have a brother?
No need to be so uptight about it.
But, yeah. I never know what to wear, so...
Huh?
- Let's at least roll up your pant legs.
- Sure.
And one more thing.
Since your outfit has a mature flare to it...
You should part your bangs.
Yeah, looks good.
The clothes are wearing me, aren't they?
That's not true.
Huh?
Be more confident in yourself.
- Hey there.
- Thanks for waiting.
No way.
Asamiya's on time for once.
I can't believe it.
He's either late, or straight up ditches
when he's got plans with us.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I'd never keep Mayama waiting.
Wow.
The power of Mayama.
Let's go.
Dang.
Asamiya, you're scaring me, dude.
Seriously.
It's all Mayama, I guess.
So, where do we start?
Any outfit ideas?
- We got great weather today.
- Yeah.
Who's outfit do we look for first?
Let's start with Mayama's costume.
Sounds good.
Maybe we'll find the rest along the way.
Does that always happen?
Only whenever Asamiya's around.
- They're not squealing at me?
- No.
For real?
- I thought I was popular.
- They clearly only care about Asamiya.
Seriously?
- Bummer...
- Cheer up, man.
Fuzzy ears?
What for?
After a heated back and forth discussion,
we agreed you'd be a werewolf.
Yeah. Try them on.
Not exactly what we imagined.
He's not scary, that's for sure.
Any thoughts, Asamiya?
He looks cute.
Werewolves aren't supposed to be cute, right?
No, it could work.
Agreed.
I'll find an outfit for you.
Asamiya's fired up about this.
Wish he'd brought that enthusiasm
when he first joined our committee.
Well, Asamiya can handle Mayama's outfit.
Let's go find something for ourselves.
Sure.
Which one will you start with?
Huh?
You all right in there?
I'm having trouble with this choker.
Hold on.
Huh?
Wait, what?
Asamiya?
Hold still.
There.
Thanks.
Perfect.
Sir?
Scare you?
[Stickout, Used Clothing]
Sakaki and Tsunekawada need more time.
All right.
Let's ditch them.
Huh?
Come on.
Vanilla, or twist. Which one?
I'll take whatever you don't pick.
You okay with vanilla?
Yeah, thanks.
I hope they don't mind that we left.
Want a bite?
Hurry, before it melts.
Okay.
It's good.
Right?
It was melting.
Anywhere you want to go? We've got time.
I'll leave it up to you.
I want to go where you want to go.
I didn't have anywhere in mind...
[Kosokodo - Used bookstore]
A bookstore?
Yeah. It's an out-of-the-way place for me.
I didn't know you liked to read.
I only read a book a month.
I learned something new today.
What about you? Do you read?
If it's a hobby of yours, I'll give it a try.
Give me a recommendation.
Sure.
Let's see...
How about this one?
Sure.
You're not going to read the summary?
I'll take this one.
That'll be 820 yen.
Let me get your change.
- Mayama.
- Yeah?
They're giving out freebies.
Really?
[Aoba Publishing Fair]
There are four designs in total.
May I have this one?
Sure thing.
Your change of 180 yen,
and your book.
Thank you, come again.
- Here.
- Huh?
You can have it.
Perfect for the name, "Hare", right?
[T/N: "Hare" means "sunny day"]
Thanks.
Give me a sec to browse, too.
Sorry, my phone was out of battery.
Sounds good.
Thanks for waiting.
Perfect timing. Sakaki and Tsunekawada
also just finished.
Sorry I took a while.
I hadn't visited in a minute,
so I couldn't stop browsing.
It's fine. I had fun seeing you so excited.
Asamiya.
Here.
This one's for you.
Your first name, "Kosei",
means "shining star", right?
So, yeah.
Our first date, and your first gift.
I could die today.
That's seriously not funny.
But you won't deny the "date" part.
What? No, well...
That's because there was lots more to rag on.
Sure, I'll leave it at that.
Thanks.
That's what I should be saying.
I had fun today. Thanks.
You have any plans after this?
I have to finish up some homework.
- Makes sense.
- Don't you?
I already finished everything.
I'm not surprised.
Well, I only did everything
because I wanted to leave the day free.
Kosei?
Hey, it's been a while!
You're as good-looking as ever.
What's up?
I'm out shopping.
Who's this?
A friend from high school.
I see.
She's a classmate from middle school.
Thanks for walking me home.
You live pretty far from school.
How about I come get you every morning?
Uh, well...
Should I not?
Yeah, please don't.
Asamiya.
You and I are...
Welcome home, Hare.
Tenn?
- Your brother...
- Oh, hey!
Is this the friend you went out with today?
My name is Kosei Asamiya.
It's an honor to meet you.
I'm Tenn Mayama, Hare's older brother.
It's nice to see Hare bring someone over.
- Is that unusual?
- Yeah.
It might honestly be a first.
How about it? Wanna come in?
It's fine. He just walked me home.
He walked you home?
I mean...
Right, that's weird.
Why would a guy walk another guy home?
I walked him back,
because I worry he's too cute.
A-Asamiya?
- I totally get you.
- Huh?
My brother's just the cutest.
He's started to get
a bit prickly around me, though.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Just the other day,
I tried to fix his bed hair,
but he refused my help!
- Cute.
- Right?
Say, can we trade numbers?
Of course.
These two...
They're the picture perfect pair.
Crap, I have a job to get to.
Hope you visit again, Asamiya.
I will, thank you.
He's a nice guy.
You two are nothing alike, though.
You can say that again.
Huh?
My brother is amazing.
He's tall, popular,
and talented, too.
But, I'm...
His brother is so talented.
- He's smart, athletic...
- Right?
It's such a wonder.
How are they related?
Mayama?
Never mind. It's nothing.
It's clearly not, "nothing". What's up?
When you confessed to me,
I think I was happy.
You're kind, and fun to hang out with.
I promise, that's no lie.
It's just...
There are better people out there for you.
But I like 'you', Mayama.
Why?
I'm a boring guy.
There's nothing special about me.
So why me?
Because you're you.
That's not an answer.
Why do I like him so much?
Here. Have this last one.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
Here you go.
Thank you.
I'll always have some in stock.
Good to know.
But I'm sure about one thing.
Mayama is my first real crush.
I don't know how I should treat you anymore.
I've never worked in a group
with friends before.
I want our haunted house to be a success.
I would find myself
looking at Mayama from afar.
It didn't take long for me to realize
what I felt for him now, was "love".
Why do you want to go out with me?
We saw the video.
Can we get a selfie together?
These comments are nasty.
People always took one look at me,
and made assumptions.
Don't use me as engagement bait.
He's just a shallow guy with the looks.
If I posted a shot of Asamiya in a dress,
I'd get crazy likes.
I don't think Asamiya would appreciate that.
Asamiya's feelings matter.
Sorry. I kept saying I liked you,
without even considering how you felt.